Office of the Boards of Advisors Records UA200
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Dental Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.005; 3.6 Linear Feet; 20 Digital Object(s) Of the 20 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 5 files and .15 MBs of data.
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Friday, November 17, 2000; UA200.005.001.00088 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, April 6, 2000; UA200.005.001.00089 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Overseers Meeting Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.005.001.00090 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board Meeting Friday, April 29, 1999; UA200.005.001.00091 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board Meeting October 29, 1998; UA200.005.001.00092 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Wednesday, May 6, 1998; UA200.005.001.00093 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Tuesday, October 7, 1997; UA200.005.001.00094 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Mtg. - April 17, 1997; UA200.005.001.00095 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Thursday, October 24, 1996; UA200.005.001.00096 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Overseers Meeting - April 24, 1996; UA200.005.001.00097 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental April 28, 1995; UA200.005.001.00098 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental - October 27, 1995; UA200.005.001.00099 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Board Mtg. Dec. 1/2, 1994; UA200.005.001.00100 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Bd. Mtg. April 28, 1994; UA200.005.001.00101 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Nov 15, 1993; UA200.005.001.00102 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental, 1992; UA200.005.001.00103 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental, 1992; UA200.005.001.00104 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental, 1991; UA200.005.001.00105 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - December 4, 1990 Mtg., UA200.005.001.00106 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Meeting, April 19, 1990; UA200.005.001.00107 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Mtg., November 14, 1989; UA200.005.001.00108 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Meeting, April 4, 1989; UA200.005.001.00109 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Dental Meeting, June 28, 1988; UA200.005.001.00110 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting, 2004-04-30; UA200.005.008.00001; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting, 2004-04-30
  - Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting, 2004-11-16; UA200.005.008.00002; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-04-07; UA200.005.008.00003; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting, April 7, 2005
  - Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-11-17; UA200.005.008.00004; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-05-05; UA200.005.008.00005; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Dental Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-10-13; UA200.005.008.00006; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Meeting of the Dental Board of Overseers, 2007-05-04; UA200.005.008.00007; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Meeting of the Dental Board of Overseers
  - Report from the Meeting of the Dental Board of Overseers, 2007-11-07; UA200.005.008.00008; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Meeting of the Dental Board of Overseers, 2008-05-02; UA200.005.008.00009; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-10-29; UA200.005.008.00010; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-05-01; UA200.005.008.00011; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-11; UA200.005.008.00012; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-04-30; UA200.005.008.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-10-27; UA200.005.008.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2011-10-19; UA200.005.008.00015; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Dental, 2007 -- 2015; UA200.005.020 (Box 20)
    Meeting agendas, minutes, and materials, Spring 2007-Spring 2015.
  - Dental, 2005 -- 2006; UA200.005.021 (Box 21)
    Meeting agendas, minutes, and materials, Spring 2005-Spring 2006.
  - Dental meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2018; UA200.005.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); .11 Megabytes
  - Dental Board of Advisors Minutes, 2018-10-12, UA200.005.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Dental Board of Advisors Minutes, 2019-04-09; UA200.005.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 29 Kilobytes
  - Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Advisors Meeting, 2019 November 15; UA200.000741; 38.86 Megabytes
  - Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Advisors Meeting, 2020 April 14; UA200.000753; 24.2 Kilobytes
- Engineering Board of Overseers, 1989 -- 2020; UA200.006; 2.4 Linear Feet; 27 Digital Object(s) Of the 27 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 5 files and .17 MBs of data.
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, October 14, 2004; UA200.006.001.00111 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers MTG. Tuesday, May 11, 2004; UA200.006.001.00112 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting Wednesday, October 29, 2003; UA200.006.001.00113 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting Thursday, April 10, 2003; UA200.006.001.00114 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday, October 22, 2002; UA200.006.001.00115 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, May 16, 2002; UA200.006.001.00116 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Tuesday, October 16, 2001; UA200.006.001.00117 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Wednesday, May 9, 2001; UA200.006.001.00118 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Thursday, October 12, 2000; UA200.006.001.00119 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Monday, May 15, 2000; UA200.006.001.00120 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.006.001.00121 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board Meeting Thursday, May 13, 1999; UA200.006.001.00122 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board Meeting November 3, 1998; UA200.006.001.00123 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Wednesday, April 15, 1998; UA200.006.001.00124 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Mtg. Wednesday, October 15, 1997; UA200.006.001.00125 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Mtg. - May 2, 1997; UA200.006.001.00126 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Friday, October 18, 1996; UA200.006.001.00127 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Eng. Mtg.- May 2, 1996; UA200.006.001.00128 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering May 2, 1995; UA200.006.001.00129 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering, 1995; UA200.006.001.00130 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Board Mtg. Oct. 24, 1994; UA200.006.001.00131 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Nov 4, 1993; UA200.006.001.00132 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Eng., 1993; UA200.006.001.00133 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Eng., 1992; UA200.006.001.00134 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering, 1992; UA200.006.001.00135 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering, 1991; UA200.006.001.00136 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Meeting, 1991; UA200.006.001.00137 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Meeting, 1990; UA200.006.001.00138 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Mtg. March 23, 1990; UA200.006.001.00139 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Engineering Mtg. June 27, 1989; UA200.006.001.00140 (Box UA200 Shared 2)
  - Minutes from the Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-04-14; UA200.006.013.00001; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Minutes from the Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Dean's Report to the Overseers Slideshow, 2005-04-14; UA200.006.013.00002; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Dean's Report to the Overseer's Slideshow
  - Minutes from the Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-10-18; UA200.006.013.00003; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Dean's Report to the Overseers Presentation, 2005-10-18; UA200.006.013.00004; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Dean's Report to the Overseers Presentation
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Marketing and Resources Task Force Update, 2005-10; UA200.006.013.00005; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Engineering Board of Overseers Marketing and Resources Task Force
  - Minutes from the Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-04-11; UA200.006.013.00006; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - SoE Finance Sources FY 06 Board present, 2006-04-01; UA200.006.013.00007; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    SoE Finance Sources FY 06 Board presentation
  - Minutes from the Tufts Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-10-18; UA200.006.013.00008; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Dean's Report, 2006-10-18; UA200.006.013.00009; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Dean's Report
  - Marketing/Resources Task Force Update, 2006-10-18; UA200.006.013.00010; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Marketing/Resources Task Force Update
  - Biology for Engineers Recommendations for an Undergraduate Course, 2006-10-18; UA200.006.013.00011; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Biology for Engineers Recommendations for an Undergraduate Course
  - Minutes from the Tufts Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-04-12; UA200.006.013.00012; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Minutes from the Tufts Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Minutes from the Tufts Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-10-10; UA200.006.013.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers, 2008-04-08; UA200.006.013.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers
  - Gordon Institute Vision and Strategy Presentation, 2008-04; UA200.006.013.00015; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Gordon Institute Vision and Strategy Presentation
  - Integrated Laboratory Complex Program, 2008; UA200.006.013.00016; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Integrated Labratory Complex Program Presentation
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-10-16; UA200.006.013.00017; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-04-14; UA200.006.013.00018
    Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-10-06; UA200.006.013.00019
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-04-08; UA200.006.013.00020; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-10-14; UA200.006.013.00021; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting, 2011-10-21; UA200.006.013.00022; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Engineering, 2005 -- 2015; UA200.006.021 (Box 21)
  - Engineering meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2018; UA200.006.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); .13 Megabytes
  - Engineering Board of Advisors Minutes, 2018-10-02, UA200.006.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Engineering Board of Advisors Minutes, 2019-05-07; UA200.006.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 30 Kilobytes
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Advisors Meeting, 2019 October 18; UA200.000742; 36.7 Megabytes
  - Report from the School of Engineering Board of Advisors Meeting, 2020 April 07; UA200.000749; 21.9 Kilobytes
- Fletcher School Board of Overseers, 1960 -- 2019; UA200.007; 2.4 Linear Feet; 23 Digital Object(s) Of the 23 digital objects in this series, 1 represents a zip file comprising 6 files and .23 MBs of data.
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting Mon.- Tues. October 18-19, 2004 Washington, DC, UA200.007.002.00001 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers MTG. Monday/Tuesday, April 26-27, 2004; UA200.007.002.00002 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Mtg. Monday, February 9, 2004-Medford, UA200.007.002.00003 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting Sunday, October 19, 2003; UA200.007.002.00004 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting Tuesday, April 29, 2003; UA200.007.002.00005 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting February 10-11, 2003- Medford Campus, UA200.007.002.00006 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting October 21-22, 2002 - Washington, DC, UA200.007.002.00007 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Mtg. April 23, 2002; UA200.007.002.00008 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting Monday, February 11, 2002; UA200.007.002.00009 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting Tuesday, October 23, 2001; UA200.007.002.00010 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting Monday, April 2, 2001; UA200.007.002.00011 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting Monday, November 13, 2000; UA200.007.002.00012 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Mtg. April 10, 2000; UA200.007.002.00013 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers meeting January 30-31, 2000; UA200.007.002.00014 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - FLETCHER BOARD OF OVERSEERS MTG. Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.007.002.00015 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - FLETCHER BOARD OF OVERSEERS MTG. Thursday, September 30, 1999; UA200.007.002.00016 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Meeting Monday, April 12, 1999; UA200.007.002.00017 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Meeting Monday, January 25, 1999; UA200.007.002.00018 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers mtg. Monday, January 26, 1998; UA200.007.002.00019 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Mtg. Monday, April 13, 1998; UA200.007.002.00020 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Meeting- October 26, 1998; UA200.007.002.00021 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Mtg. - April 14, 1997; UA200.007.002.00022 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Mtg. Monday, October 20, 1997; UA200.007.002.00023 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers Wednesday, January 8, 1997; UA200.007.002.00024 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Visitors Thursday, October 3, 1996; UA200.007.002.00025 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board of Visitors Monday, April 29, 1996; UA200.007.002.00026 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher - October 30, 1995; UA200.007.002.00027 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher May 1, 1995; UA200.007.002.00028 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - FLETCHER MEETING - October 24, 1994; UA200.007.002.00029 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - October '93 Fletcher, 1993; UA200.007.002.00030 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. Monday, October 17, 1988; UA200.007.002.00031 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Meeting Monday, April 28, 1986; UA200.007.002.00032 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Meeting Thurdday, April 18, 1985; UA200.007.002.00033 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Meeting Tuesday, October 15, 1985; UA200.007.002.00034 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Meeting October 9, 1984; UA200.007.002.00035 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Meeting April 5, 1984; UA200.007.002.00036 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Meeting November 1, 1983; UA200.007.002.00037 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. May 21, 1976; UA200.007.002.00038 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. December 17, 1976; UA200.007.002.00039 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. May 7, 1975; UA200.007.002.00040 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. December 16, 1974; UA200.007.002.00041 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. November 4, 1968; UA200.007.002.00042 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. April 29, 1968; UA200.007.002.00043 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. September 20, 1967; UA200.007.002.00044 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. December 9, 1960; UA200.007.002.00045 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Fletcher Board Mtg. May 18, 1960; UA200.007.002.00046 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-02-08; UA200.007.014.00001; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-04-26; UA200.007.014.00002; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-10-17; UA200.007.014.00003; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-05-04; UA200.007.014.00004; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-10-17; UA200.007.014.00005; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-02-12; UA200.007.014.00006; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-04-24; UA200.007.014.00007; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2007-10-23; UA200.007.014.00008; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-02-11; UA200.007.014.00009; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-04-29; UA200.007.014.00010; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2008-10-12; UA200.007.014.00011; Boards of Overseers Office
    The Cosmos Club Washington, DC
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-02-09; UA200.007.014.00012; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-05-15; UA200.007.014.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-10-20; UA200.007.014.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report on the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-02-08; UA200.007.014.00015; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report on the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report on the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-05-21; UA200.007.014.00016; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report on the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-10-15; UA200.007.014.00017; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report on the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2011-10-04; UA200.007.014.00018; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report on the Fletcher Board of Overseers Meeting, 2012-02-10; UA200.007.014.00019; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Fletcher, 2005 -- 2015; UA200.007.022 (Box 22)
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers meeting minutes, 1996 -- 2001; UA200.007.030; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 30)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by the Office of the Boards of Advisors, 2018, accession UA-2018-065.
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers meeting minutes, 2001 -- 2006; UA200.007.031; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 31)
    20 years from the date of creation.
  - Fletcher Board of Overseers meeting minutes, 2007; UA200.007.032; .2 Linear Feet (Box 32)
  - Fletcher meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2018; UA200.007.00001; 6 Digital Object(s); .23 Megabytes
  - Fletcher BOA Minutes, 2018-10-19, UA200.007.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Fletcher BOA Minutes, 2019-03-01; UA200.007.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 41 Kilobytes
  - Fletcher Meeting Minutes, 2019-05-17; UA200.007.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 37 Kilobytes
- International Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.008; 3.6 Linear Feet; 12 Digital Object(s) Of the 12 digital objects in this series, 1 represents a zip file comprising 4 files and .12 MBs of data.
  - International Board of Overseers Tufts in Mexico, November 11-14, 2004 [Binder], UA200.008.002.00047 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers MTG. Friday/Saturday, November 12-13, 2004; UA200.008.002.00048 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers MTG. Friday/Saturday, June 11-12, 2004; UA200.008.002.00049 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Mtg. November 14, 2003-Boston/Medford, UA200.008.002.00050 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Informal Session-London, England Tuesday, January 21, 2003; UA200.008.002.00051 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Mtg. Canceled Toranto, Canada-April 7-8, 2003; UA200.008.002.00052 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Mtg. June 23-24, 2002 - Talloires, France, UA200.008.002.00053 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Mtg. November 6-7, 2001-Medford Campus, UA200.008.002.00054 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Mtg.-Prague, Czech Republic April 27-28, 2001; UA200.008.002.00055 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Board Book, Prage [Binder], UA200.008.002.00056 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Mtg. Washington, DC - November 15-16, 2000; UA200.008.002.00057 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Mtg. April 30-May 4, 2000 Florence, Italy, UA200.008.002.00058 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - INTERNATIONAL BOARD OF OVERSEERS MTG. Friday, November 5, 1999; UA200.008.002.00059 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board Meeting Madrid, Spain April 5-8, 1999; UA200.008.002.00060 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board Meeting November, 3-4,1998, UA200.008.002.00061 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International, UA200.008.002.00062 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers Meeting September 22-24, 1997 BOSTON, UA200.008.002.00063 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Mtg. - April 2, 3, 4 1997 - Hong Kong, UA200.008.002.00064 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International Board of Overseers November 6,7,8, 1996; UA200.008.002.00065 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - INTERNATIONAL BOARD OF OVERSEERS April 10 -12, 1996; UA200.008.002.00066 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International, 1995; UA200.008.002.00067 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - SEPT. 21-23, 1994 INTERNATIONAL BOARD MTG, UA200.008.002.00068 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International meeting, 1994; UA200.008.002.00069 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International meeting - Sept.93 Monte Carlo, 1993; UA200.008.002.00070 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International meeting, 1993; UA200.008.002.00071 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International meeting- October 15-16, 1992; UA200.008.002.00072 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International meeting- April 9, 1992; UA200.008.002.00073 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International meeting, 1991; UA200.008.002.00074 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International meeting, 1991; UA200.008.002.00075 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Internat'l Meeting, Nov. 29 & 30, 1990; UA200.008.002.00076 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - International meeting, 1990; UA200.008.002.00077 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Intl. Mtg. - February 2-3, 1990; UA200.008.002.00078 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Intl. Mtg., - Sept. 28-29, 1989; UA200.008.002.00079 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Intl. Mtg. - May 17-19, 1989; UA200.008.002.00080 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Intl. Mtg., 1988; UA200.008.002.00081 (Box UA200 Shared 3)
  - Report from the International Board of Overseers Meeting, Mexico City, Mexico, 2004-11-12; UA200.008.009.00001; Boards of Overseers Office
  - Report from the International Board of Overseers Meeting-Tufts European Center, Talloires, France, 2005-06-10; UA200.008.009.00002; Boards of Overseers Office
    Report from the International Board of Overseers Meeting- Tufts European Center
  - Media Activity Report for Tufts in India, 2005-11-01; UA200.008.009.00003; Boards of Overseers Office